# Julia Alonso Martínez

Project Manager



Valencia, Spain

## **Contact**

Phone number: +31 630 22 18 22

Email: alonsomartinezjulia.1988@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/julia-alonso-martínez-13828b128

# **Summary**

I have several years of experience in Customer Service, developing a strong sense of responsibility, organization and empathy towards stakeholders.

With a degree in History, after several years working with customers, I have specialized in Project Management, being certified by the Project Management Institute (PMI), Scrum.org and Google.

I am currently working as a project manager at AVALNET. In addition, I work at the PMI as a volunteer and I am studying the Official Master's Degree In project Management at the European University of Valencia.

# **Professional Experience**

• 10/2022 – Present Project Manager

**AVALNET** 

Project management; customer management; project requirement definition; project coordination; e-mail marketing; agile.

• 05/2022 – 10/2022 Project Manager

Freelance (self-employed)

Scrum master; project requirement definition; project coordination; requirements gathering; customer management.

• 07/2021 – 12/2021 Administrative Salesperson

Gana Energía

Customer management; incidences management and resolution; contract process monitoring; contract management; customer acquisition.

• 06/2017 – 07/2021 Specialist agent in telephone customer service

Atento España

Customer management; incidences resolution; appointment scheduling.

• 12/2015 – 05/2017 Agent in telephone customer service

Atento España

Customer management; incidences resolution.

## Volunteering

• 06/2023 – Present **Project Management Institute**PMI Levante, Spain Chapter

### Education

- 2022 2023 **Master's Degree, Project Management** Universidad Europea. Valencia, Spain
- 2013 2015 **Higher Education Training Cycle, Sign Language Interpretation** CIFP Misericordia. Valencia, Spain
- 2006 2011 Bachelor of Arts (BA), History Speciality in Ancient History Universitat de Valéncia. Valencia, Spain

## Licenses and certifications

Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)

Project Management Institute. July 2022

Professional Scrum Master I (PSM I)

Scrum.org. July 2022

• OKR Certified Professional OKRCP

CertiProf. Professional Knowledge. August 2022

 Google Digital Marketing & E-commerce – Seven-course Professional Certificate

Google – Coursera. September 2022

• Agile with Atlassian Jira

Atlassian. June 2022

- Google Project Management Six-course Professional Certificate
  Google Coursera. May 2022
- Digitization applied to the productive sector

CEPYME. December 2021

### Courses

- Practical English course What's Up! Academy
- OKR Goal Setting: The Complete Guide to OKRs Udemy
- Professional English for customer service Servef
- Library and Archives Technician IVEP

## Languages

- German A1 Level of the Common European Framework Reference for Languages (CEFR). German Center (Centro Alemán). July 2017
- Cambridge First Certificate in English (FCE) B2 level of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages (CEFR). 2016
- Intermediate Grade in Valencian Level C1 of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages. (CEFR). 2014